<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Classical Songs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favorite_list">FavoriteList</string>
    <string name="home_activity">BEETHOVEN</string>
    <string name="first_list">MOZART</string>
    <string name="second_list">CHOPIN</string>
    <string name="fourth_activity">OTHER</string>
    <string name="all_activity">ALL SONGS</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/7802943730</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id_allsongs">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/6002540068</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id_beethoven">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/1392037753</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id_mozart">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/2578300372</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id_chopin">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/7639055366</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id_other">ca-app-pub-2081856024983169/3372507291</string>
    <string name="info">Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western culture,
        including both liturgical (religious) and secular music.he Classical era, from about 1750 to 1820, established many
        of the norms of composition, presentation, and style, and was also when the piano became the predominant keyboard instrument.
        The basic forces required for an orchestra became somewhat standardized (although they would grow as the potential of a wider
        array of instruments was developed in the following centuries). Chamber music grew to include ensembles with as many as
        8 to 10 performers for serenades. Opera continued to develop, with regional styles in Italy, France, and German-speaking lands.
        The opera buffa, a form of comic opera, rose in popularity. The symphony came into its own as a musical form, and the concerto
        was developed as a vehicle for displays of virtuoso playing skill. Orchestras no longer required a harpsichord (which had been
        part of the traditional continuo in the Baroque style), and were often led by the lead violinist (now called the concertmaster).
        Wind instruments became more refined in the Classical era. While double-reed instruments like the oboe and bassoon became somewhat
        standardized in the Baroque, the clarinet family of single reeds was not widely used until Mozart expanded its role in orchestral,
        chamber, and concerto settings.[55]
    </string>
    <string name="BeethovenInfo">Ludwig van Beethovenbaptised 17 December 1770[1] – 26 March 1827)
        was a German composer and pianist. A crucial figure in the transition between the Classical and Romantic eras
        in Classical music, he remains one of the most recognised and influential of all composers.
    Born in Bonn, then the capital of the Electorate of Cologne and part of the Holy Roman Empire,
        Beethoven displayed his musical talents at an early age and was taught by his father Johann van Beethoven
        and by composer and conductor Christian Gottlob Neefe. At the age of 21 he moved to Vienna,
        where he began studying composition with Joseph Haydn and gained a reputation as a virtuoso pianist.
        He lived in Vienna until his death. By his late 20s his hearing began to deteriorate, and by the last decade of his
        life he was almost completely deaf. In 1811 he gave up conducting and performing in public but continued to compose;
        many of his most admired works come from these last 15 years of his life.</string>

    <string name="MozartInfo">Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (27 January 1756 – 5 December 1791)
    was a prolific and influential composer of the classical era.
        Born in Salzburg, Mozart showed prodigious ability from his earliest childhood. Already competent
        on keyboard and violin, he composed from the age of five and performed before European royalty.
        At 17, Mozart was engaged as a musician at the Salzburg court, but grew restless and traveled in search of
        a better position. While visiting Vienna in 1781, he was dismissed from his Salzburg position.
        He chose to stay in the capital, where he achieved fame but little financial security.
        During his final years in Vienna, he composed many of his best-known symphonies, concertos, and operas, and portions
        of the Requiem, which was largely unfinished at the time of his early death at the age of 35. The circumstances of his
        early death have been much mythologized.
        He composed more than 600 works, many acknowledged as pinnacles of symphonic, concertante, chamber, operatic, and
        choral music.
        He is among the most enduringly popular of classical composers, and his influence is profound on subsequent Western
        art music. Ludwig van Beethoven composed his own early works in the shadow of Mozart, and Joseph Haydn wrote:
        "posterity will not see such a talent again in 100 years".</string>

    <string name="ChopinInfo">Fryderyk Franciszek Chopin – the most outstanding Polish composer and pianist,
        born in the village of Żelazowa Wola in the district of Sochaczew. The composer and his family held his date of
        birth to be 1 March 1810, yet the certificate of baptism signed in the parish church of Brochów is dated 22 February.
        That discrepancy has still not been entirely resolved, although today it is the date celebrated by Chopin and his
        family that is more often used. Chopin’s first piano teacher, Adalbert Zywny, had already introduced him to the music
        of Bach and the Viennese classics. As a pianist, however, Chopin is considered to have been self-taught:
        he doesn’t seem to have needed to practise very much. His more extended early works were decorative and brilliant,
        in the line of display pieces by touring virtuosos like Hummel. After giving two big concerts in Warsaw at which he
        introduced his two piano concertos, Chopin left for Vienna in November 1830, staying eight months, during which he
        learnt of the Warsaw Uprising. He never saw Poland again. He made his way to Paris, where he soon felt at home,
        since there were many Polish émigrés in the French capital. His music sold well, and from 1833 it was published
        simultaneously in England, France and Germany. Chopin wrote Nocturnes and shorter pieces in dance forms, such as Mazurkas, Waltzes and Polonaises, throughout his career.
        He found his mature style early, with the first set of Études, Op. 10 (1829–32). These are still, with their sequel,
        the Op. 25 set, the cornerstone of modern piano technique, as well as powerfully poetic pieces.</string>

</resources>
